Guide to the George Mason University Plan for Alternative General Education records, 1983-1998
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
George Mason University Plan for Alternative General Education records
1983-1998
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
George Mason University Plan for Alternative General Education
R0014
16 linear feet (32 boxes)
Collection contains photographs, PAGE publications, articles on PAGE, and correspondence within PAGE.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by George Mason Universtiy.
Historical Information
In 1983, George Mason University established the Plan for Alternative General Education (PAGE). It was a program that provided entering freshmen an alternative way to fulfill the general education requirements of the university. It was an interdisciplinary, forty-five credit, two-year curriculum, which integrated knowledge from various academic disciplines.
At its peak PAGE enrolled 250 new students each year and aimed to provide a sense of community and unity among students and faculty that was seen to be missing at large state academic institutions. In the spring of 1997, the College of Arts and Sciences and the George Mason University Faculty Senate voted to convert PAGE into an honors program. And on May 15, 1998, the last PAGE class graduated, ending its existence.
PAGE's fifteen-year existence was innovative and forward- thinking for its time. Its innovative spirit could be seen in its approach to course design and in methods of teaching, which included a interdisciplinary approach to teaching.PAGE was recognized for its success in providing an creative approach to higher education when, in 1986, it received the G. Theodore Mitau Award for Innovation and Change in Higher Education from the Association of American State Colleges and Universities.
Scope and Content
Collection contains photographs, PAGE publications, articles on PAGE, and correspondence within PAGE.
Arrangement
Orgnaized by subject.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives holds the George Mason University records.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
George Mason University. Plan for Alternative General Education.
Subjects:
Universities and colleges--Curricula--Virginia.
Contents List
- George Mason University Plan for Alternative General Education records
  - Classified Staff (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence 1984-85 (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - Page Computing (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - M.L. King (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - Page Exit Interviews 1994-95 (Folder 5, Box 1)
  - P121 Readings in Order (Folder 6-7, Box 1)
  - Faculty Meeting 1-19-93 (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - FTE (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - Gilbert, Harvey Strand (Folder 10, Box 1)
  - Page Goals Statement- Cby Courses 1994 (Folder 11, Box 1)
  - Page Grants Materials (Folder 12, Box 1)
  - Grant Prospects (Folder 13, Box 1)
  - HS Transition Papers (Folder 14, Box 1)
  - Modern Documents (Folder 15, Box 1)
  - NCCCE/Page Agreement (Folder 1, Box 2)
  - Newsletter to Students, August 1994 (Folder 2, Box 2)
  - Page Schematic Diagram (Folder 3, Box 2)
  - Preview (Folder 4, Box 2)
  - Robinson Professors (Folder 5, Box 2)
  - Sexual Harassment Procedures (Folder 6, Box 2)
  - Strand F91 (Folder 7, Box 2)
  - Strand 1993 (Lancaster) (Folder 8, Box 2)
  - TDC (Folder 9, Box 2)
  - Teaching Effectiveness (Folder 10, Box 2)
  - TA Applications (Folder 11, Box 2)
  - University Center Building, GMU (Folder 12, Box 2)
  - WAC in PAGE, 1992-93 (Folder 13, Box 2)
  - ZBC Project (Folder 14, Box 2)
  - Parking Services Information Guide (Folder 15, Box 2)
  - Administrative Procedures and Emergencies (Folder 16, Box 2)
  - Budget (Folder 17-18, Box 2)
  - Bylaws (Folder 19, Box 2)
  - CAC/WAC Grant from CAS (Open Date)- Pat Story (Folder 20, Box 2)
  - CAS(College of Arts and Sciences) Bylaws, March 1993 (Folder 21, Box 2)
  - CAS 1994 (Folder 1, Box 3)
  - CAS 1993-94 (Folder 2, Box 3)
  - CAS 1992-93 (Folder 3, Box 3)
  - Course Headers 1983-84 (Folder 4, Box 3)
  - Executive Committee Meeting (Past) 1986-87 (Folder 5, Box 3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings (Past) 5-5-87 (Folder 6, Box 3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings (Past)- Cancelled 5-4-87 (Folder 7, Box 3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings (Past)- Cancelled 4-20-87 (Folder 8, Box 3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings (Past) 4-6-87, 3-23-87, 3-2-87, 2-23-87, 2-9-87, 2-1-87, 11-17-86, 11-3-86, 10-20-86, 2-29-86, 9-15-86, 5-1-86, 4-16-86, 4-3-86, 3-19-86, 3-6-86, 2-19-86 (Folder 9-25, Box 3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings (Past) 2-6-86, 1-22-86, 12-4-85, 11-13-85, 11-6-85, 10-30-85, 10-16-85, 10-9-85, 9-24-85, 9-4-85, 5-16-85, 5-9-85, 4-25-85, 3-28-85, 2-28-85 (Folder 26-40, Box 3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings (Past) 1-24-85, 12-13-84, 12-5-84, 11-11-84, 10-4-84, 9-20-84, 9-6-84, 8-21-84 (Folder 1-9, Box 4)
  - Faculty Attitude Survey- Control (Folder 10, Box 4)
  - Attitude Survey- Page Faculty (Folder 11-12, Box 4)
  - Attitude Survey- Comments From Survey Forms (Folder 13, Box 4)
  - Faculty Attitude Survey- Control S84 (Inactive) (Folder 14, Box 4)
  - Attitude Surveys- Freshman (Folder 15, Box 4)
  - Attitude Surveys- Student Comments (Folder 16, Box 4)
  - Attitude Surveys Nos.1, 2, 3 Compiled (Folder 17, Box 4)
  - Faculty Attitude Survey White S84 (Folder 18, Box 4)
  - Faculty Attitude Survey Beige S84 (Folder 19, Box 4)
  - Executive Committee (Folder 1, Box 5)
  - Executive Committee S92 (Folder 2, Box 5)
  - Courses (Folder 3-4, Box 5)
  - Retreat (Folder 5, Box 5)
  - 250 (Folder 1-2, Box 6)
  - XX 141 A1 C.1. (Folder 3, Box 6)
  - XX 957 A1 C.1 (Folder 4, Box 6)
  - XX 141 A1 C.2 (Folder 5, Box 6)
  - XX 141 A2 C.2 (Folder 6, Box 6)
  - XX 141 A2 C.1 (Folder 7, Box 6)
  - XX 141 A2 C.3 (Folder 8, Box 6)
  - XX 957 A1 C.2 (Folder 9, Box 6)
  - Reserve Readings for Page 252 (Dicerbo) (Folder 10-13, Box 6)
  - Reading- Page 253 Spring- Contemporary United States (Folder 14, Box 6)
  - Ways of Seeing (Folder 15, Box 6)
  - Body Ritual Among the Nacirema (Folder 16, Box 6)
  - The Interpretation of Cultures (Folder 17, Box 6)
  - Interpersonal Relations Between Kin (Folder 18, Box 6)
  - The Trends: Marriage, Divorce, Remarriage (Folder 19, Box 6)
  - Transparency Film (Folder 20, Box 6)
  - Gender and Popular Culture (Folder 1, Box 7)
  - Executive Summary (Folder 2, Box 7)
  - Proposal to National Endowment for the Humanities (Folder 3-6, Box 7)
  - Proposal for Funds for Excellence (Folder 4, Box 7)
  - Plan for Alternative General Education (PAGE) (Folder 5-7, Box 7)
  - Page Summer Seminar for Faculty Development (Folder 8, Box 7)
  - The Methodological Position of Symbolic Interactionism (Folder 9, Box 7)
  - The Stanford Prison Experiment (Folder 10, Box 7)
  - Accomplices to the Crime (Folder 11-12, Box 7)
  - Mejia, Kiane Elizabeth 861 (Folder 13, Box 7)
  - S84 151/153 Exam I (Folder 14, Box 7)
  - Community Organizers and Social Planners (Folder 15, Box 7)
  - Community Organizers and Voluntary Associations (Folder 16, Box 7)
  - Power and Pluralism: A View From the Bottom (Folder 17, Box 7)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development- Schedule (Folder 1, Box 8)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development- Participants and Contracts (Folder 2, Box 8)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development- Announcements (Folder 3, Box 8)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development- Evaluations (Folder 4, Box 8)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development (Folder 5, Box 8)
  - Fall 1982- Spring 1983 (Folder 1, Box 9)
  - Summer Seminar 1982 (Folder 2, Box 9)
  - Early 1983 Course Proposal (Folder 3-4, Box 9)
  - Sumsem General Education Seminar (Folder 5, Box 9)
  - Summer Seminar 1987- Space (Folder 6, Box 9)
  - Sumsem 1987 Ideas Submitted by Faculty (Folder 7, Box 9)
  - Report of the 1987 Page Faculty Workshop/Orientation (Folder 8, Box 9)
  - 1986 Summer Seminar Report (Folder 9, Box 9)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development (Folder 10, Box 9)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development- Additional Information and Materials (Folder 11, Box 9)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development- Report (Folder 12, Box 9)
  - Sumsem 1986 Page Seminar for Faculty Development- Course Material (Folder 13, Box 9)
  - Foundation Information (Folder 1-4, Box 10)
  - Software for Writing in Page (Folder 5, Box 10)
  - Home Package for CT (Folder 6, Box 10)
  - Summer Plans (Folder 7, Box 10)
  - Summer 1984 Handouts (Back Copies) (Folder 8, Box 10)
  - YLQSRO JO15 (Folder 9, Box 10)
  - Minutes- Reports, April 1983-84 (Folder 10, Box 10)
  - Participants of Page Summer Seminar for Faculty Development (Folder 1, Box 11)
  - Page Summer Seminar for Faculty Development (Folder 2, Box 11)
  - 1984-1988 Statistics on Page Student Data- Math and Verbal Test Scores (Folder 3-5, Box 11)
  - General Education Goals (Folder 6, Box 11)
  - Summer Workshop for Page Faculty 1988- Visions and Revisions (Folder 7, Box 11)
  - Edvc 313- Fall 1983 Syllabus (Folder 8, Box 11)
  - Evaluation Articles, etc. (Folder 9, Box 11)
  - Course Syllabi- Fall 1983 and Spring 1984 (Folder 10, Box 11)
  - Summer 1983 Partial Information (Folder 1, Box 12)
  - Summer 1983 Evaluations Forms (Folder 2-3, Box 12)
  - Sumsem 1985 Page Seminar for Faculty Development (Folder 4-6, Box 12)
  - Participants for Page Summer Seminar for Faculty Development (Folder 7-8, Box 12)
  - Executive Committee (Folder 1, Box 13)
  - Page- HP (Folder 2, Box 13)
  - ADE- 1983 (Folder 3, Box 13)
  - Student Recruitment (Folder 4, Box 13)
  - Library (Folder 5, Box 13)
  - Newsletter (Folder 6, Box 13)
  - Language Lecture (Folder 7, Box 13)
  - NCTE 1982 (Folder 8, Box 13)
  - Summer 1983 (Folder 9, Box 13)
  - Page Computer (Folder 10, Box 13)
  - Writing- x- Civic (Folder 11, Box 13)
  - Page Courses 3-9-83 (Folder 12, Box 13)
  - A 2/4 Fall- Spring 1982-83 (Folder 13, Box 13)
  - Dime Novel (Folder 14, Box 13)
  - Dr. Jan Cohn (Folder 15, Box 13)
  - Page- Summer 1984 (Folder 1, Box 14)
  - Strand Lectures Spring 1984 (Folder 2, Box 14)
  - Page Course Evaluations (Folder 3, Box 14)
  - Executive Committee 1984 (Folder 4, Box 14)
  - Funds for Excellence Proposal 2-1-84 (Folder 5, Box 14)
  - Mention: Notable Programs (Folder 6, Box 14)
  - Page Promotional (Folder 7, Box 14)
  - Page- Formal Evaluation (Folder 8, Box 14)
  - Faculty Evaluations, Spring 1984 (Folder 9, Box 14)
  - Faculty Survey, Fall 1983 (Folder 10, Box 14)
  - Sports (Folder 11, Box 14)
  - Budget- Prof. Cohn (Folder 12, Box 14)
  - Reading Romance (Folder 13, Box 14)
  - Summer 1983 (Folder 14, Box 14)
  - Page Spring 1989 Syllabi (Folder 1, Box 15)
  - Page and Your Major an Advising Book for Faculty and Students, Fall 1987 (Folder 2, Box 15)
  - Page and Your an Advising Book for Faculty and Students, Fall 1988 (Folder 3, Box 15)
  - Page and Your Major and Advising Book for Faculty and Students, Fall 1989 (Folder 4, Box 15)
  - Page 123, 1984 (Folder 6-7, Box 15)
  - Page- Course Headers (Folder 8, Box 15)
  - Page 1988 (Folder 1, Box 16)
  - Curriculum- Planning June 1981- December 1981 (Folder 2, Box 16)
  - Page- 1984, 1985, Summer 1986, 1989 (Folder 3-6, Box 16)
  - Course Prospectus (Folder 7, Box 16)
  - Page Reading Assignments (Folder 8, Box 16)
  - Faculty (FTE) (Folder 1, Box 17)
  - Page Executive Committee (Folder 2-3, Box 17)
  - Dean/Chairs (Folder 4-5, Box 17)
  - Faculty Inventory (Folder 1-2, Box 18)
  - Administration Student Survey Done in S87 (Folder 3, Box 18)
  - Faculty Workshop, January 1992 (Folder 4, Box 18)
  - Page Executive Committee (Folder 5, Box 18)
  - University Writing (Folder 6, Box 18)
  - Faculty (FTE) (Folder 8, Box 18)
  - Page Reading (Folder 1, Box 19)
  - F84 Student Surveys Responses (Folder 2-3, Box 19)
  - General Proposal 1981-82 (Folder 4-5, Box 19)
  - Faculty Inventory, etc. (Folder 6, Box 19)
  - Prof. Duara- Marketing and Social Structure in Rural China (Buklet) (Folder 1, Box 20)
  - Arthur P. Wolf- Gods, Ghosts, and Ancestors (Folder 2, Box 20)
  - Prof. Duara- Chinese Towns (Folder 3, Box 20)
  - Document 9: Each Tribe Can Seen as a Nation (Folder 4, Box 20)
  - Francois- Noel Babeauf and the Conspiration Des Egaux (Folder 5, Box 20)
  - Transperency Copies- Atmosphere- Water- Oceans (Folder 6, Box 20)
  - Overhead Transparencies- Dr. Hayden- Water Planet- The Ocean (Folder 7, Box 20)
  - Qualitative Analysis: Water in Hydrates (Folder 8, Box 20)
  - The Quantum Mechanics of Black Hole (Folder 9, Box 20)
  - Symbiotic Stars- Scientific American (Folder 10, Box 20)
  - Decision Making Processes (Folder 11, Box 20)
  - Measurement in Observational Research (Folder 12, Box 20)
  - The "In-Charge Complex" and Tobian Political Culture (Folder 13, Box 20)
  - An Overview of the Earth and Its Atmosphere (Folder 14, Box 20)
  - Thick Description: Toward an Interpretive (Folder 15, Box 20)
  - Mediterranean Sea (Folder 16, Box 20)
  - A Phenomenological Study of Suicide Notes (Folder 17, Box 20)
  - Araby (Folder 18, Box 20)
  - Brief on Growth (Folder 19, Box 20)
  - The Sisters (Folder 20, Box 20)
  - Determinism and Free Will (Folder 21, Box 20)
  - The Methodological Position of Symbolic Interactionism (Folder 22, Box 20)
  - How to Solve it Understanding the Problem (Folder 23, Box 20)
  - Saints and Heroes (Folder 24, Box 20)
  - Interview After the Performance (Folder 25, Box 20)
  - Death of a Salesman (Scene From) (Folder 26, Box 20)
  - Electronic Mail Coming at You - John Seaman (Folder 27, Box 20)
  - Europe's Human Approach- Peter Krass (Folder 28, Box 20)
  - New Worlds of Computer- Mediated Work- S. Hoshana Zuboff (Folder 29, Box 20)
  - How to Design With the User in Mind- Ben Schneiderman (Folder 30, Box 20)
  - What Users Want- John A. Moynihan (Folder 31, Box 20)
  - The Mechanization of Office Work- Vincent E. Giuliano (Folder 1, Box 21)
  - Nine Principles for Ergonomic Software- Louis Fried (Folder 2, Box 21)
  - Common Sense Knowledge- Harold Sarfinkel (Folder 3, Box 21)
  - What Rights Do We Have? (Folder 4, Box 21)
  - What Is a Language?- Charles E. Osgood (Folder 5, Box 21)
  - For the Characters Are Myself- Negro American Literature (Folder 6, Box 21)
  - Lab Exercise No. 1- Properties of the Atmosphere (Folder 7, Box 21)
  - Physical and Chemical Changes- Prof. Ed Johnson (Folder 8, Box 21)
  - Nadeau, Fall 1984 (Folder 9, Box 21)
  - Landforms (Laboratory Exercise)- Dr. Hayden (Folder 10, Box 21)
  - Introduction to Minerals (Folder 12, Box 21)
  - The Hubble Law of Expansion of the Universe- Stellar Structure and Luminosity (Folder 12, Box 21)
  - Field Trips- Rocks of Virginia (Folder 13, Box 21)
  - Earth History (Folder 14, Box 21)
  - Geology Labs- Dr. Mose (Folder 15, Box 21)
  - Field Trips- Rocks Formed by the Opening of Atlantic Ocean (Folder 16, Box 21)
  - The Clustering of Galaxies (Folder 1, Box 22)
  - The Science of Geography (Folder 2, Box 22)
  - Atomic Spectra (Folder 3, Box 22)
  - Astronomical Facts- Dr. Kaftos (Folder 4, Box 22)
  - Introduction to Some Basic Concepts of Logic (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - Phases in the Development of Industrialized States (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - The Faith vs. Reason Conflict (Folder 7, Box 22)
  - Article Deep Play: Notes on Balinese Cockfight (Folder 8, Box 22)
  - The Birth of Khadi (Folder 9, Box 22)
  - Walden Two- S.F. Skinner (Folder 10, Box 22)
  - The Revolt of the Masses (Folder 11, Box 22)
  - Conceptions of Self (Folder 12, Box 22)
  - Readings- Fall 1987 (Folder 13, Box 22)
  - Taking Rights Seriously (Folder 14, Box 22)
  - Strange Things Happen Here (Folder 15, Box 22)
  - Sigmund Freud and Psychoanalysis (Folder 16, Box 22)
  - Nothing Unusual is Happening- Joan M. Peterson (Folder 17, Box 22)
  - The Mind in Love: Dante's Philosophy (Folder 18, Box 22)
  - The Methodological Position of Symbolic Interactionism (Folder 19, Box 22)
  - Inferno (Folder 20, Box 22)
  - Human Freedom and the Self (Folder 21, Box 22)
  - Hinduism- "Religions of Man" by Smith (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - Has the 'Free Will'? by Campbell (Folder 2, Box 23)
  - Free Will in Theory and Practice (Folder 3, Box 23)
  - Dramas of Selfhood in Comedy (Folder 4, Box 23)
  - Determinism and Free Will (Folder 5, Box 23)
  - Dante's Conception of Love (Folder 6, Box 23)
  - Becoming a Marihuana User by Horward S. Becker (Folder 7, Box 23)
  - Booklet (Reproduced)- Introduction to Models in the Social Sciences (Folder 8, Box 23)
  - Prof. Rosenblum- Accomplices to the Crime (Folder 9, Box 23)
  - Reading the Arts (Folder 10, Box 23)
  - Prof. Comito- Symphony No.5 in E Minor, "From the New World" (Folder 2, Box 24)
  - A Travesty Generator for Micros (From Byte) (Folder 2, Box 24)
  - Computers in Contemporary Society (Folder 3, Box 24)
  - Page 120- Readings- Fall 1987 (Folder 4, Box 24)
  - Class Photo 1992-94 (Folder 5, Box 24)
  - Class Photo 1994-95 (Folder 6, Box 24)
  - Class Photo 1995-97 (Folder 7, Box 24)
  - Class Photo 1996-98 (Folder 8, Box 24)
  - Page Program's Student Newspaper April 1995 (Folder 9, Box 24)
  - Commemoration for the Closing Reception (Folder 1, Box 25)
  - Class Photos (Folder 3, Box 25)
  - Student Awards Ceremony (Folder 3, Box 25)
  - 1994 Picnic Photos (Folder 4, Box 25)
  - Photos (Folder 5, Box 25)
  - Honors "Picnic" May 1999 (Folder 6, Box 25)
  - Contact Sheets (Folder 7, Box 25)
  - Correspondence and Social History of Page (Folder 8, Box 25)
  - Spring 1995 Earth Day- Photos Taken by Bill Lankford (Folder 9, Box 25)
  - Correspondence (Folder 10, Box 25)
  - Designing the Page Program for the Future (Folder 11, Box 25)
  - Photo Negatives (Folder 12, Box 25)
  - Slide and Photo Negative (Folder 13, Box 25)
  - Slides (Folder 14, Box 25)
  - Glenda Kirkman- Page Photos and Slides (Folder 15, Box 25)
  - Slides (Folder 16, Box 25)
  - Exhibition (Copy) (Folder 17, Box 25)
  - Slides (Folder 1, Box 26)
  - Correspondence- General Education Evaluation Committee (Folder 2, Box 26)
  - Correspondence Articles on Page and Photos (Folder 3, Box 26)
  - Correspondence- Articles of Interest (Folder 4, Box 26)
  - Correspondence- Articles About Page (Folder 5, Box 26)
  - Correspondence- Publicity (Folder 6, Box 26)
  - Correspondence- 10th Anniversary, 1993 (Folder 7, Box 26)
  - Administration- Inventory of Page- Related Work (Folder 8, Box 26)
  - Students Reinstatement Letters (Folder 9, Box 26)
  - Student Guidelines for Page Lounge (Folder 10, Box 26)
  - Administration- Students- Questionnaire/Demographies (Folder 11, Box 26)
  - Administration- Students- Data Questionnaire 1987 (Folder 12, Box 26)
  - Correspondence- Mitav Award (Folder 13, Box 26)
  - Correspondence- Datatel User's Manual (Folder 14, Box 26)
  - Occoteek Cleanup- Spring 1995 (Folder 15, Box 26)
  - Photos (Folder 16-17, Box 26)
  - Faculty (Folder 18, Box 26)
  - Scheduling of Courses (Folder 1, Box 27)
  - Course Proposals (Folder 2, Box 27)
  - Miscellaneous Page Materials (Folder 3, Box 27)
  - Memos (Folder 4, Box 27)
  - Page- B2 (Folder 5, Box 27)
  - Page- Strands (Folder 6, Box 27)
  - Page- Board of Visitors (Folder 7, Box 27)
  - Page- Grants (Folder 8, Box 27)
  - Faculty Interactions CAS (Folder 9, Box 27)
  - Catalog Copy (Folder 10, Box 27)
  - Accepted Page Students (Folder 1, Box 28)
  - Sample Schedules (Folder 2, Box 28)
  - Counseling (Folder 3, Box 28)
  - A5/A7- Page (Folder 4, Box 28)
  - A5/A7 Current Course Proposal (Folder 5, Box 28)
  - Sara Looney- Advising- Grant Application (Folder 6, Box 28)
  - A8 (Folder 7, Box 28)
  - Page B4 (Folder 8, Box 28)
  - Page B3 (Folder 9, Box 28)
  - Audio Visual Materials (Folder 10, Box 28)
  - AAC- Baltimore Conference (Folder 11, Box 28)
  - Association of American Colleges (Folder 12, Box 28)
  - Jerry Gaff- General Education Today (Folder 13, Box 28)
  - Page- Constructive (and Other) Criticism (Folder 1, Box 29)
  - Page- Correspondence Outside University (Folder 2, Box 29)
  - Page- High Schools (Folder 3, Box 29)
  - General Education- Reference (Folder 4, Box 29)
  - Course Prospectus (Folder 5, Box 29)
  - General Education at Other Schools (Folder 6, Box 29)
  - P.R. (Folder 7, Box 29)
  - General Education- Course Proposals (Folder 8, Box 29)
  - Class Schedules- GMU (Folder 9, Box 29)
  - Art Commission (Folder 10, Box 29)
  - Page B1 (Folder 11, Box 29)
  - Page A3/A6 (Folder 12, Box 29)
  - Page A2/A4 (Folder 13, Box 29)
  - Page A1 (Folder 14, Box 29)
  - Page- Evaluation (Folder 15, Box 29)
  - Chris Theiss- Writing/ Warren Decker- Speaking (Folder 1, Box 30)
  - ICPSR (Folder 2, Box 30)
  - Broadside (Folder 3, Box 30)
  - Recruitment (Folder 4, Box 30)
  - Summer 1982 (Folder 5, Box 30)
  - Faculty Senate (Folder 6, Box 30)
  - A5/A7 Reform Council (Folder 7, Box 30)
  - Joint Review Committee (Folder 8, Box 30)
  - CPS (Folder 9, Box 30)
  - Notes From Elizabeth (Folder 1, Box 31)
  - School of Business Administration (Folder 2, Box 31)
  - Interdisciplinary/Non Traditional Programs Council (Folder 3, Box 31)
  - Early Admitted Student Reception (Folder 4, Box 31)
  - Meeting Attendance Spring 1983 (Folder 5, Box 31)
  - Proposal (Folder 6, Box 31)
  - Curriculum Committee- CAS (Folder 7, Box 31)
  - Curriculum 'Snapshot" 2-2-83 - 2-9-83 (Folder 8, Box 31)
  - Page Meeting Times (Folder 9, Box 31)
  - Page 227- Lecture 1984 (Folder 10, Box 31)
  - Page- Inventory 1984 (Folder 11, Box 31)
  - Page 227- Lecture Fall 1985 (Folder 12, Box 31)
  - Page- Genetics Lab (Folder 13, Box 31)
  - Science Course, 1984 (Folder 14, Box 31)
  - Page Office (Folder 15, Box 31)
  - Notes From Jan- Executive Meeting (Folder 16, Box 31)
  - Flyer (Folder 17, Box 31)
  - Oral Communications (Folder 18, Box 31)
  - Book I (Folder 19, Box 31)
  - Director to Page Faculty Memos (Folder 20, Box 31)
  - Campus Memos (Folder 1, Box 32)
  - Dean CAS (Folder 2, Box 32)
  - V.P. for Academic Affairs (Folder 3, Box 32)
  - Newsletter No.2 (Folder 4, Box 32)
  - Orientation 1983 (Folder 5, Box 32)
  - The Mason Gazette (Folder 6, Box 32)
  - General Faculty (Folder 7, Box 32)
  - Spring 1985 Syllabi (Folder 8, Box 32)
  - Fall 1984 Syllabi (Folder 9, Box 32)
  - Fall 1985 Syllabi (Folder 10, Box 32)